socialannex.com 2019-12-16

# Annex Cloud Privacy Policy

Effective date: December 1, 2019

Social Annex, Inc. dba Annex Cloud ("us", "we", or "our") operates the <https://www.annexcloud.com/> website (the "Service").

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use our Service and the choices you have associated with that data.

We use your data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible from <https://www.annexcloud.com/>

#### **Definitions**

  * ##### **Service**

Service is the <https://www.annexcloud.com/> website operated by Social Annex, Inc. dba Annex Cloud 

  * ##### **Personal Data**

Personal Data means data about a living individual who can be identified from those data (or from those and other information either in our possession or likely to come into our possession). 

  * ##### **Usage Data**

Usage Data is data collected automatically either generated by the use of the Service or from the Service infrastructure itself (for example, the duration of a page visit). 

  * ##### **Cookies**

Cookies are small pieces of data stored on your device (computer or mobile device). 

  * ##### **Data Controller**

Data Controller means the natural or legal person who (either alone or jointly or in common with other persons) determines the purposes for which and the manner in which any personal information are, or are to be, processed. 

For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, we are a Data Controller of your Personal Data. 

  * ##### **Data Processors (or Service Providers)**

Data Processor (or Service Provider) means any natural or legal person who processes the data on behalf of the Data Controller. 

We may use the services of various Service Providers in order to process your data more effectively. 

  * ##### **Data Subject (or User)**

Data Subject is any living individual who is using our Service and is the subject of Personal Data. 

#### Information Collection and Use 

We collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our Service to you. 

#### Types of Data Collected

##### **Personal Data**

While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you ("Personal Data"). Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to: 

    * Email address
    * First name and last name
    * Phone number
    * Cookies and Usage Data

We may use your Personal Data to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send. 

##### **Usage Data**

We may also collect information how the Service is accessed and used ("Usage Data"). This Usage Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data. 

##### **Tracking & Cookies Data**

We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service and hold certain information. 

Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Service. 

You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service. 

Examples of Cookies we use:

    * **Session Cookies.** We use Session Cookies to operate our Service.
    * **Preference Cookies.** We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various settings.
    * **Security Cookies.** We use Security Cookies for security purposes.

#### Use of Data

Social Annex, Inc. dba Annex Cloud uses the collected data for various purposes:

    * To provide and maintain our Service
    * To notify you about changes to our Service
    * To allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service when you choose to do so
    * To provide customer support
    * To gather analysis or valuable information so that we can improve our Service
    * To monitor the usage of our Service
    * To detect, prevent and address technical issues
    * To provide you with news, special offers and general information about other goods, services and events which we offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or enquired about unless you have opted not to receive such information

#### Legal Basis for Processing Personal Data Under General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)

If you are from the European Economic Area (EEA), Social Annex, Inc. dba Annex Cloud legal basis for collecting and using the personal information described in this Privacy Policy depends on the Personal Data we collect and the specific context in which we collect it.

Social Annex, Inc. dba Annex Cloud may process your Personal Data because:

    * We need to perform a contract with you
    * You have given us permission to do so
    * The processing is in our legitimate interests and it's not overridden by your rights
    * To comply with the law

#### Retention of Data

Social Annex, Inc. dba Annex Cloud will retain your Personal Data only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use your Personal Data to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations (for example, if we are required to retain your data to comply with applicable laws), resolve disputes, and enforce our legal agreements and policies. 

Social Annex, Inc. dba Annex Cloud will also retain Usage Data for internal analysis purposes. Usage Data is generally retained for a shorter period of time, except when this data is used to strengthen the security or to improve the functionality of our Service, or we are legally obligated to retain this data for longer time periods. 

#### Transfer of Data 

Your information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction. 

If you are located outside United States and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the data, including Personal Data, to United States and process it there. 

Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer. 

Social Annex, Inc. dba Annex Cloud will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information. 

#### Disclosure of Data

##### **Business Transaction**

If Social Annex, Inc. dba Annex Cloud is involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, your Personal Data may be transferred. We will provide notice before your Personal Data is transferred and becomes subject to a different Privacy Policy. 

##### **Disclosure for Law Enforcement**

Under certain circumstances, Social Annex, Inc. dba Annex Cloud may be required to disclose your Personal Data if required to do so by law or in response to valid requests by public authorities (e.g. a court or a government agency). 

##### **Legal Requirements**

Social Annex, Inc. dba Annex Cloud may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: 

    * To comply with a legal obligation
    * To protect and defend the rights or property of Social Annex, Inc. dba Annex Cloud
    * To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service
    * To protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public
    * To protect against legal liability

#### Information Related to Data Collected through the Social Annex, Inc. dba Annex Cloud Service

##### **Information Related to Data Collected for our Clients:**

    * Social Annex, Inc. dba Annex Cloud collects information under the direction of its Clients (Data Controllers), and has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal information it processes. If you are a customer of one of our Clients and would no longer like to be contacted by one of our Clients that use our service, please contact the Client that you interact with directly. We may transfer personal information to companies that help us provide our service. Transfers to subsequent third parties are covered by the service agreements with our Clients. 

##### **Access and Retention of Data Controlled by our Clients:**

    * Social Annex, Inc. dba Annex Cloud acknowledges that you have the right to access your personal information. Social Annex, Inc. dba Annex Cloud has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal information it processes. An individual who seeks access, or who seeks to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data should direct his query to the Social Annex, Inc. dba Annex Cloud Client (the data controller). 
    * Social Annex, Inc. dba Annex Cloud will retain personal information we process on behalf of our Clients for as long as needed to provide services to our Client. Social Annex, Inc. dba Annex Cloud will retain this personal information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

#### Security of Data

The security of your data is important to us but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

#### "Do Not Track" Signals 

We do not support Do Not Track ("DNT"). Do Not Track is a preference you can set in your web browser to inform websites that you do not want to be tracked. 

You can enable or disable Do Not Track by visiting the Preferences or Settings page of your web browser 

#### Your Data Protection Rights Under General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)

If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA), you have certain data protection rights. Social Annex, Inc. dba Annex Cloud aims to take reasonable steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your Personal Data. 

If you wish to be informed what Personal Data we hold about you and if you want it to be removed from our systems, please contact us. 

In certain circumstances, you have the following data protection rights: 

    * **The right to access, update or to delete the information we have on you.** Whenever made possible, you can access, update or request deletion of your Personal Data directly within your account settings section. If you are unable to perform these actions yourself, please contact us to assist you. 
    * **The right of rectification.** You have the right to have your information rectified if that information is inaccurate or incomplete.
    * **The right to object.** You have the right to object to our processing of your Personal Data.
    * **The right of restriction.** You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal information.
    * **The right to data portability.** You have the right to be provided with a copy of the information we have on you in a structured, machine-readable and commonly used format.
    * **The right to withdraw consent.** You also have the right to withdraw your consent at any time where Social Annex, Inc. dba Annex Cloud relied on your consent to process your personal information.

Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before responding to such requests. 

You have the right to complain to a Data Protection Authority about our collection and use of your Personal Data. For more information, please contact your local data protection authority in the European Economic Area (EEA). 

#### Service Providers

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service ("Service Providers"), to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used. 

These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose. 

In the context of onward transfers of data to third parties, Annex Cloud has responsibility for the processing of personal information it receives under Privacy Shield and subsequently transfers to a third party acting as an agent on our behalf. Annex Cloud shall remain liable under the Principles if its agent processes such personal information in a manner inconsistent with the Principles, unless Annex Cloud proves it is not responsible for the event giving rise to damage. 

#### Analytics 

We may use third-party Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Service. 

##### **Google Analytics**

Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Service. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network. 

You can opt-out of having made your activity on the Service available to Google Analytics by installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. The add-on prevents the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js, and dc.js) from sharing information with Google Analytics about visits activity. 

For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: <http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/>

#### Behavioral Remarketing 

Social Annex, Inc. dba Annex Cloud uses remarketing services to advertise on third party websites to you after you visited our Service. We and our third-party vendors use cookies to inform, optimize and serve ads based on your past visits to our Service. 

    * ##### **Google AdWords**

Google AdWords remarketing service is provided by Google Inc. 

You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize the Google Display Network ads by visiting the Google Ads Settings page:<http://www.google.com/settings/ads>

Google also recommends installing the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on - <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout> \- for your web browser. Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on provides visitors with the ability to prevent their data from being collected and used by Google Analytics. 

For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: <http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/>

    * ##### **Facebook**

You can learn more about interest-based advertising from Facebook by visiting this page: <https://www.facebook.com/help/164968693837950>

To opt-out from Facebook's interest-based ads follow these instructions from Facebook:<https://www.facebook.com/help/568137493302217>

Facebook adheres to the Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising established by the Digital Advertising Alliance. You can also opt-out from Facebook and other participating companies through the Digital Advertising Alliance in the USA  <https://www.aboutads.info/choices/>,the Digital Advertising Alliance of Canada in Canada or the European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance in Europe <http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/>, or opt-out using your mobile device settings. 

For more information on the privacy practices of Facebook, please visit Facebook's Data Policy:<https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation>

#### Links to Other Sites

Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit 

We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third-party sites or services. 

#### Children's Privacy

Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 18 ("Children"). 

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 18. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers. 

#### Changes to This Privacy Policy

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. 

We will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the "effective date" at the top of this Privacy Policy. 

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. 

You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

#### Social Annex, Inc. adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles.

##### **Privacy Policy: EU-US and Swiss-US Privacy Shields**

Social Annex, Inc. complies with the EU-US and Swiss-US Privacy Shield Frameworks as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from the European Union member countries and Switzerland, respectively. Social Annex, Inc. has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles of Notice, Choice, Accountability for Onward Transfer, Security, Data Integrity and Purpose Limitation, Access, and Recourse, Enforcement and Liability. If there is any conflict between the policies in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification page, please visit <https://www.privacyshield.gov/>

In compliance with the EU-US and Swiss-US Privacy Shield Principles, Social Annex, Inc. commits to resolve complaints about privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. European Union and/or Swiss individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding this privacy policy should first contact Social Annex, Inc at:[ info@annexcloud.com ](mailto:info@annexcloud.com) or (866-802-8806) 

Social Annex, Inc has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the EU-US and Swiss-US Privacy Shield Principles to ICDR/AAA, an alternative dispute resolution provider located in the United States and operated by the International Centre for Dispute Resolution, American Arbitration Association. If you do not receive timely acknowledgement of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed, please visit [ http://go.adr.org/privacyshield.html ](http://go.adr.org/privacyshield.html) for more information and to file a complaint. 

Please note that if your complaint is not resolved through these channels, under limited circumstances, a binding arbitration option may be available before a Privacy Shield Panel. 

Social Annex, Inc. is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the Federal Trade Commission (FTC). In certain situations, Social Annex, Inc. may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements. 

#### Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us: 

  * By email: [privacy@annexcloud.com](mailto:privacy@annexcloud.com)
